#### Contact

vsconte@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/veronica-c-967011ab (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
Public Speaking
Microsoft Office

# Veronica Conte

Travel Nephrology Nurse at Fresenius Medical Care North America Greater Philadelphia

#### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, OASIS, Coaching, Case Management, and Team Building. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing from Wesley College.

### Experience

Travel Nurse Registered Nurse

Fresenius Medical Care North America Travel Nephrology Nurse June 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Delaware
Field Nurse Case Manager
August 2016 - June 2017 (11 months)
Delaware

Fresenius Medical Care North America Nephrology Nurse August 2015 - August 2016 (1 year 1 month) Delaware

MeadowWood Behavioral Health Hospital Psychiatric Charge Nurse March 2014 - March 2016 (2 years 1 month)

## Education

Northwestern State University

Bachelor's degree, Psychology

Wesley College

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing